stargatewars.com 2015-04-19

# GateWars_Main :: Privacy

|    

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

### Information Collection and Use

#### Information Collection

GateWars_Main is the sole owner of the information collected on GateWars_Main. GateWars_Main collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

#### Registration

In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give a valid email address. We use this information to verify that the user is not attempting to gain an unfair advantage by registering multiple accounts automatically in his/her name. 

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and databases. 

**We will never give, sell, or realease information collected through this site to other parties**  

####  Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site, however, their ability to experience the site will be severely limited because cookies are an integral part of our site’s authentication system. 

#### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service. We use an analysis utility that uses log files to analyze traffic and user movement. 

### Communications from the Site

#### Account Activation

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username, and that the e-mail address they have provided is in fact a valid e-mail address. 

#### Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. We reserve the right to send an e-mail to our users if, for instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

#### Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email, in accordance with the users wishes. All emails will come from an email ending in GateWars_Main.com - if not, do not assume the email is from us.

#### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, GateWars_Main, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

#### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](mailto:admin@gatewars.com). 

| Privacy Policy | Contact Us | Terms of Service |   
_Brought to you by Kingdom Games Ltd._  
note: no images are from copyrighted sources; we are not affiliated with any TV or movie company; if it doesn't say 'Kingdom Games' on the site, it is not ours.   
ServerIP: 66.147.239.243
